Guide to the Riverwalk Jazz Collection ARS.0129
Archive of Recorded Sound
- Program research recordings
  - Fats Waller
    - Fats Waller, Bob Vincent And Me, 1 audiocassette (Audio 139)
    - Fats Waller. Rare Broadcasts; Interview 1941, 1 audiocassette (Audio 139)
    - Fats Waller For Donna Zajone. Credit: Hazen Schumacher, WUOM, Ann Arbor, 1 audiocassette (Audio 139)
    - Fats Waller. Rochester Interview 6/19/1941, Los Angeles; This Is New York, CBS 12/11/1938 (From Radiola LP); Fats Waller Program, NBC 7/5/1938 New York; Personally, It's Off The Record. WABC 9/23/1943 New York; V-Discs 9/1943, 1938-1943; 1 audiocassette (Audio 139)
  - Harry Warren Speaks, 2002; 1 CD-R (Audio 134)
  - Eulogy For Conoly P. Watson, 1984; 1 audiocassette (Audio 139)
  - Lu Watters
    - Air Checks. Lu Watters, This Is Jazz 8/16/1947; Turk Murphy Live At Easy Street November 1958, 1 audiocassette (Audio 139)
    - Phil Elwood's Tape of Lu Watters Excerpts, 1 audiocassette (Audio 139)
    - Watters - KPFA Use. 1957 Show #1; From Hambone's 1949-1950, 1 audiocassette (Audio 139)
  - Bob Wilber and Benny Carter Shows Cassette and Disc Transfers, 1992-03-04; 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 5)
  - This Is Jazz. Bob Wilber, 1947-04-19; 2 audiocassettes (Audio 139)
  - Spiegle Willcox
    Willcox, Spiegle
    - Spiegle Willcox Interview, 1993-03-12; 1 DAT (Audio 44)
    - Spiegle Willcox Interview. Venuti Pre-Production Tape, 1993-03-12; 1 audiocassette (Audio 139)
  - Lee Wiley. You're A Sweetheart. GeezerJazz, 1 CD-R (Audio 86)
  - Teddy Wilson Interview From Cassettes, 2006-04-25; 2 CD-Rs (Audio 86)
- Program concepts
  Various folders of proposals and ideas for programs, many of which also contain research and historical background. Some were originally filed as "Hot Productions," meaning they were in active development. Many concepts were never realized. There are also files about potential compilation or rebroadcast programs.
  - Misc. Compilation Shows, 1 folder (Box 220)
  - Misc. Show Ideas binder, 5 folders (Box 220)
  - 1994 Ideas, 1 folder (Box 221)
  - 1998 Ideas, 1 folder (Box 221)
  - 1999-2000 Ideas, 1 folder (Box 221)
  - 2000 Ideas, 1 folder (Box 221)
  - 2002 Ideas, 1 folder (Box 221)
  - 2004 Ideas, 2 folders (Box 221)
  - Don Albert, 1 folder (Box 221)
  - American In Paris/Hyman, 1 folder (Box 221)
  - American Spirit, 1 folder (Box 221)
  - Maya Angelou, 1 folder (Box 221)
  - Louis Armstrong, 5 folders (Box 221)
  - Band - Original, 1 audiocassette (Box 221)
  - Bob Barnard, 1 folder (Box 221)
  - Bix, 2 folders (Box 221)
  - Black Nativity/Langston Hughes, 1 folder (Box 222)
  - Boogie Woogie '98, 1 folder (Box 222)
  - Chris Botti, 1 folder (Box 222)
  - Brainstorm With Band, 2003; 1 folder (Box 221)
  - Bronzeville, 1 folder (Box 222)
  - Sebastian Campesi, 1 folder (Box 222)
  - Doc Cheatham, 1 folder (Box 222)
  - C.G. Conn, 1 folder (Box 222)
  - Jim Cullum Compilation, 1 folder (Box 222)
  - Stephen Foster, 2 folders (Box 222)
  - Johnny Frigo/Jazz Violin, 1 folder (Box 222)
  - Vince Giordano, 1 folder (Box 222)
  - Golden Rod Riverboat, 1 folder (Box 222)
  - Grappelli/Reinhardt, 1 folder (Box 222)
  - Guys And Dolls, 1 folder (Box 222)
  - Gregory Hines, 1 folder (Box 222)
  - Milt Hinton, 1 folder (Box 222)
  - Tish Hinojosa, 1 folder; 1 CD-R (Box 222)
  - The Horn Palace, 1 folder (Box 222)
  - Hot Record Society, 1 folder (Box 222)
  - Jazz Ambassadors, 1 folder (Box 222)
  - Jazz Roots 1905-1920, 1 folder (Box 222)
  - Jukebox, 1 folder; 1 computer disk (Box 222)
  - Gus Kahn, 1 folder (Box 222)
  - Narvin Kimball, 1 folder (Box 222)
  - Listener Ideas And Input, 1 folder (Box 220)
  - Stranger Malone, 1 folder (Box 222)
  - Joe McBride, 1 folder (Box 222)
  - Marian McPartland, 2 folders (Box 222)
  - Jay McShann, 1 folder (Box 222)
  - Midwest Jazz, 1 folder (Box 222)
  - Music is My Mistress/Duke Ellington, 1 folder (Box 222)
  - Willie Nelson, 1 folder (Box 222)
  - David Newman, 1 folder (Box 223)
  - Red Norvo, 1 folder (Box 223)
  - On The Road, 1 folder (Box 223)
  - Armand J. Piron, 1 folder (Box 223)
  - Railroads, 1 folder (Box 223)
  - Lucky Roberts, 1 folder (Box 223)
  - Willard Robison, 1 folder (Box 223)
  - Rodgers and Hart/Becky Kilgore, 1 folder (Box 223)
  - Duncan Schiedt, 1 folder (Box 223)
  - Lavay Smith, 1 folder (Box 223)
  - Songs Of Italy, 1 folder (Box 223)
  - Richard Sudhalter, 2 folders (Box 223)
  - Talking Blues, 1 folder; 1 CD-R (Box 223)
  - Trombone Shorty, 1 folder (Box 223)
  - Sophie Tucker, 1 folder (Box 223)
  - Lu Watters, 1 folder (Box 223)
  - Joe Wilder, 1 folder; 3 CD-Rs (Box 223)
  - Bob Wills, 1 folder (Box 223)
- Biographical files
  Background information on musicians and other guests, including article and review clippings, media kits, resumes/CVs, demo recordings, and photographs (including a few RWJ originals and negatives). Not all those listed were necessarily featured on programs. Also included are biographies of Riverwalk's producer Margaret Pick, host David Holt, bandleader Jim Cullum and selected members of the Jim Cullum Jazz Band (other sometime members are listed among guests).
  - Miscellaneous: Music Arranging, 1 folder (Box 162)
  - Miscellaneous: Actors Audition Tape [for Willie The Lion Smith role], 1991; 1 folder; 1 audiocassette (Box 162)
  - Producer: Margaret Pick [Press; Photos; Bio; Resume], 6 folders; 2 computer disks (Box 162)
  - Host: David Holt, 2 folders (Box 162)
  - Jim Cullum Jazz Band members
    - Miscellaneous, 1 folder (Box 162)
    - Jim Cullum [Memoir; Correspondence; Bio], 3 folders (Box 162)
    - Kevin Dorn, 1 folder (Box 162)
    - Howard Elkins, 1 folder (Box 162)
    - Ron Hockett, 1 folder (Box 162)
    - Don Mopsick, 1 folder (Box 162)
    - Kenny Rupp, 1 folder (Box 162)
    - John Sheridan, 1 folder (Box 162)
    - Ed Torres, 1 folder (Box 162)
    - Jim Turner, 1 folder (Box 162)
    - Mike Waskiewicz, 1 folder (Box 162)
  - Abel, Alan, 1 folder (Box 163)
  - Alden, Howard, 1 folder (Box 163)
  - Allen, Rex, 1 folder (Box 163)
  - Allred, Bill, 1 folder (Box 163)
  - Atkins, Chet, 1 folder (Box 163)
  - Ashby, Harold, 1 folder (Box 163)
  - Avakian, George, 1 folder (Box 163)
  - Baker, Clint, 1 folder (Box 163)
  - Barnard, Bob, 1 folder (Box 163)
  - Bagneris, Vernel, 2 folders; 1 CD-R (Box 163)
  - Barrett, Dan, 1 folder (Box 163)
  - Barrett, Darren, 1 folder (Box 163)
  - Bennett, David, 1 folder (Box 163)
  - Blaine, Terry, 1 folder (Box 163)
  - Boston, Gretha, 1 folder (Box 163)
  - Boswell Sisters, 1 folder (Box 163)
  - Bradford, Carmen, 1 folder; 2 audiocassettes (Box 163)
  - Bridgett, Darren, 1 folder (Box 163)
  - Brunious, John, 1 folder; 1 audiocassette (Box 163)
  - Burrell, Terry, 1 folder (Box 163)
  - Butler, Henry, 1 folder (Box 163)
  - Caldwell, Jesse, 1 folder (Box 163)
  - Calloway, Cab, 1 folder (Box 163)
  - Capobianca, John, 1 folder (Box 163)
  - Carelli, Gerard, 1 folder (Box 163)
  - Carmichael, Judy, 1 folder; 1 audiocasette; 1 compact disk (Box 163)
  - Carter, Benny, 1 folder (Box 163)
  - Chapman, Topsy, 1 folder (Box 164)
  - Cheatham, Doc, 1 folder (Box 164)
  - Chenille Sisters, 1 folder (Box 164)
  - Christopher, Evan, 1 folder (Box 164)
  - Clooney, Rosemary, 1 folder (Box 164)
  - Cocuzzi, John, 1 folder (Box 164)
  - Cole, Natalie, 1 folder (Box 164)
  - Cuesta, Henry, 1 folder (Box 164)
  - Dapogny's Chicago Jazz Band, 1 folder (Box 164)
  - Davern, Kenny, 1 folder (Box 164)
  - Dirty Dozen Brass Band, 1 folder (Box 164)
  - Driver, Minnie, 1 folder (Box 164)
  - Edison, Harry "Sweets", 1 folder (Box 164)
  - Five By Design, 1 folder; 1 compact disc (Box 164)
  - Feather, Lorraine, 1 folder (Box 164)
  - Fenneman, George, 1 folder (Box 164)
  - Ferro, Nina, 1 folder (Box 164)
  - Fireworks Jazz Band, 1 folder (Box 164)
  - Fraser, Brendan, 1 folder (Box 164)
  - Freeberg, Stan, 1 folder (Box 164)
  - Frigo, Johnny, 1 folder (Box 164)
  - Frishberg, Dave, 1 folder; 1 audiocassette; 1 compact disc (Box 164)
  - Fulton Street Jazz Band, 1 folder (Box 164)
  - Gibson, Banu, 2 folders; 2 audiocassettes; 1 compact disc (Box 164)
  - Gimble, Johnny, 1 folder (Box 165)
  - Giordano, Vince, 1 folder (Box 165)
  - Glover, Savion, 1 folder (Box 165)
  - Grappelli, Stephane, 1 folder (Box 165)
  - Grey, Al, 1 folder; 1 audiocassette (Box 165)
  - Grosz, Marty, 1 folder (Box 165)
  - Hackett, Bobby, 1 folder (Box 165)
  - Haggart, Bob, 1 folder (Box 165)
  - Hampton, Lionel, 1 folder (Box 165)
  - Haran, Mary Cleere, 1 folder (Box 165)
  - Harris, Hilda, 1 folder (Box 165)
  - Havens, Bob, 1 folder (Box 165)
  - Havens, Richie, 1 folder (Box 165)
  - Henderson, Joe, 1 folder (Box 165)
  - Hentoff, Nat, 1 folder (Box 165)
  - Hinton, Milt, 1 folder (Box 165)
  - Hirt, Al, 1 folder (Box 165)
  - Hopkins, Linda, 1 folder (Box 165)
  - Horn, Shirley, 1 folder (Box 165)
  - Horton, Joanne, 1 folder (Box 165)
  - Hot Club of San Francisco, 1 folder (Box 165)
  - Hucko, Peanuts, 1 folder (Box 165)
  - Humphrey, Willie, 1 folder (Box 165)
  - Hyman, Dick, 1 folder (Box 165)
  - Independence Hall Jazz Band, 1 folder (Box 166)
  - Jackson, Franz, 1 folder (Box 166)
  - Jacquet, Illinois, 1 folder (Box 166)
  - Jones, Connie, 1 folder (Box 166)
  - Kellso, Jon-Eric, 1 folder (Box 166)
  - Kilgore, Rebecca, 1 folder (Box 166)
  - Kitt, Eartha, 1 folder (Box 166)
  - Lage, Julian, 1 folder (Box 166)
  - Laughlin, Tim, 1 folder (Box 166)
  - Lea, Barbara, 1 folder; 1 compact disc (Box 166)
  - Maheu, Jack, 1 folder (Box 166)
  - Marcovicci, Andrea, 1 folder (Box 166)
  - Margolis, Kitty, 1 folder (Box 166)
  - Marsalis, Ellis, 1 folder (Box 166)
  - Marsalis, Branford, 1 folder (Box 166)
  - Marsalis, Wynton, 1 folder (Box 166)
  - McCorkle, Susannah, 1 folder (Box 166)
  - McCorvey, Samuel, 1 folder; 1 audiocassette; 1 videocassette (Box 166)
  - McFerrin, Bobby, 1 folder (Box 166)
  - McPartland, Marian, 1 folder (Box 166)
  - Miller, Hazel, 1 folder; 1 audiocassette (Box 166)
  - Morath, Max, 1 folder (Box 166)
  - Motley, Byron, 1 folder (Box 166)
  - McShann, Jay, 1 folder (Box 166)
  - Nakasian, Stephanie, 1 folder (Box 166)
  - Niemack, Judy, 1 folder (Box 166)
  - Nichols, Gary, 1 folder (Box 166)
  - Oakley, Leon, 1 folder (Box 166)
  - Odetta, 1 folder (Box 167)
  - Ogilvie, Brian, 1 folder (Box 167)
  - Park, Peyton, 1 folder (Box 167)
  - Payton, Nicholas, 1 folder (Box 167)
  - Pearl Django, 1 folder (Box 167)
  - Peplowski, Ken, 1 folder; 1 audiocassette (Box 167)
  - Peters, Bernadette, 1 folder (Box 167)
  - Phillips, Russ, 1 folder (Box 167)
  - Pittsley, Mike, 1 folder (Box 167)
  - Pizzarelli, Bucky, 1 folder (Box 167)
  - Pizzarelli, John, 1 folder (Box 167)
  - Previn, Andre, 1 folder (Box 167)
  - Rawls, Lou, 1 folder (Box 167)
  - Reaves-Philips, Sandra, 1 folder (Box 167)
  - Ringwald, Molly, 1 folder (Box 167)
  - Rise And Shine, 1 folder (Box 167)
  - Roberts, Lynn, 1 folder; 2 audiocassettes (Box 167)
  - Roberts, Marcus, 1 folder (Box 167)
  - Robinson, David, 1 folder (Box 167)
  - Rosene, Barbara, 1 folder; 1 compact disc (Box 167)
  - Saloff, Spider, 1 folder (Box 167)
  - Smith, Lavay, 1 folder (Box 167)
  - Smith, Phil, 1 folder; 1 audiocassette (Box 167)
  - Stein, Andy, 1 folder (Box 168)
  - Stewart, Bob, 1 folder (Box 168)
  - Stewart, Phillip, 1 folder (Box 168)
  - Sutton, Ralph, 1 folder (Box 168)
  - Taylor, Billy, 1 folder (Box 168)
  - Teagarden, Norma, 1 folder (Box 168)
  - Terry, Clark, 1 folder (Box 168)
  - Thompson, Butch, 1 folder (Box 168)
  - Tidaback, Darrel, 1 folder (Box 168)
  - Uptown Lowdown Jazz Band, 1 folder (Box 168)
  - Vachand#233;, Allan, 1 folder (Box 168)
  - Vachand#233;, Warren, 1 folder (Box 168)
  - Varon, Charlie, 1 folder (Box 168)
  - Vereen, Ben, 1 folder (Box 168)
  - Vuckovich, Larry, 1 folder (Box 168)
  - Walter, Cory, 1 folder (Box 168)
  - Walbridge, Mike, 1 folder (Box 168)
  - Wallach, Eli, 1 folder (Box 168)
  - Ward, Helen, 1 folder (Box 168)
  - Warfield, William, 1 folder (Box 168)
  - Washam, Veronica M., 1 folder (Box 168)
  - Wilber, Bob, 1 folder (Box 168)
  - Wilder, Joe, 1 folder (Box 168)
  - Willcox, Spiegle, 1 folder (Box 168)
  - Williams, Joe, 1 folder (Box 168)
  - Williams, Roosevelt T., 1 folder (Box 168)
  - Wilson, Cassandra, 1 folder (Box 168)
  - Woods, Carol, 1 folder (Box 168)
  - Wyatt, Jack, 1 folder (Box 168)
  - Yankee, Pat, 1 folder (Box 168)
  - Yerba Buena Stompers, 1 folder (Box 168)
  - The Landing, San Antonio, 1990-2007
    - 1990-1991
      Archive DATS Sent By Jim Anderson 5/2003.
      - Jazz on the Radio. Bob Crosby Show Rehearsal, 1990-05-05; 1 DAT (Audio 52)
      - Jazz Guitar Show Rehearsal, 1990-06-02; 1 DAT (Audio 52)
      - San Antonio Stomp Off. Rehearsal, Show and Edited Safety With Spot, 1990-06-28; 3 DATs (Audio 52)
      - Jazz Train Rehearsal, 1990-06-30; 1 DAT (Audio 52)
      - Texas Big T Rehearsal and Show, 1990-08-02; 2 DATs (Audio 52)
      - Kansas City Big Blues Rehearsal, 1990-08-04; 1 DAT (Audio 52)
      - Lionel Hampton Rehearsal and Show, 1990-10-08; 2 DATs (Audio 52)
      - Sidney Bechet Rehearsal, 1991-02-09; 1 DAT (Audio 52)
      - Earl Hines/Hoagy Safety, 1 DAT (Audio 52)
      - Riverwalk Cuts: Ellington and Bechet, 1 DAT (Audio 52)
    - 1996
      - Harlem Rhapsody Rehearsal, 1996-09-09; 3 DTRS tapes (Audio 53)
      - Harlem Rhapsody Show, 1996-09-10; 3 DTRS tapes (Audio 53)
      - Lenox To Broadway Rehearsal, 1996-09-10; 3 DTRS tapes (Audio 53)
      - Lenox To Broadway Show, 1996-09-10; 3 DTRS tapes (Audio 53)
      - Gospel in Jazz Rehearsal, 1996-09-11; 3 DTRS tapes (Audio 53)
      - Gospel in Jazz Show, 1996-09-11; 3 DTRS tapes (Audio 53)
    - 1997
      - Landing Concert With Nina Ferro. Afternoon Set 1, 6/4; Night Set 1 and 2, 6/4; Rehearsal, 6/5,; Show Sets 1-4, 6/5, 1997-06; 11 DAT (Audio 53)
      - Set 1 Night 6/4; Set 2 Night 6/4; Set 3, Pick Ups 6/4; Afternoon 6/5; Show #1 6/5; Show #2 6/5, 1997-06; 6 audiocassettes (Audio 136)
    - 1998
      - Jazz Pianists of the Swing Era. Rehearsal 12/15 and Show 12/16 [note: title is crossed out on rehearsals], 1998-12; 6 DTRS tapes (Audio 53)
      - Jazz Pianists of the Swing Era. Riverwalk Live, San Antonio, Texas. Malcolm's Field Recording, 1998-12-16; 1 audiocassette (Audio 136)
      - New Orleans Rhythm Kings Rehearsal and Show, 1998-12-16; 6 DTRS tapes (Audio 54)
      - New Orleans Rhythm Kings. Riverwalk Live, San Antonio, Texas. Malcolm's Field Recording, 1998-12-16; 1 audiocassette (Audio 136)
    - 1999
      - Big City Jazz in the 40s: Armstrong/Teagarden. Rehearsal and Show, 1999-04-07; 6 DTRS tapes (Audio 54)
      - Back Roads of Texas Jazz: Teagarden. Rehearsal and Show, 1999-04-07; 6 DTRS tapes (Audio 54)
    - 2000
      - Afternoon Rehearsals 3/7, 3/8, 2000-03; 3 DTRS tapes; 3 DATs (Audio 54)
      - Greenwich to 52nd Street, 2000-03-08; 3 DTRS tapes; 3 DATs (Audio 54)
      - Long Way From St. Louis. Rehearsal and Show, 2000-03-08; 3 DTRS tapes; 2 DATs; 1 CD-R (Audio 54, Audio 81)
      - Riverwalk Rehearsal 11/15-16, 2000-11; 3 DTRS tapes; 6 DATs (Audio 55)
      - Swinging With The Eel. Show, 2000-11-16; 3 DTRS tapes; 2 DATs; 1 CD-R (Audio 55, Audio 81)
      - Mr. Fazola and Mr. Miller. Show and Playbacks, 2000-11-16; 4 DTRS tapes; 2 DATs; 1 CD-R (Audio 81, Audio 55)
    - 2001
      - Ace Of Rhythm: Jabbo Smith Show. Rehearsals 3/7-8; Show 3/8, 2001-03; 3 DTRS tapes; 5 DATs; 1 CD-R (Audio 81, Audio 55)
      - Brass Bands and Funerals: Danny Barker Show. Rehearsals 3/7-8 and Show 3/8, 2001-03; 3 DTRS tapes; 4 DATs; 1 CD-R (Audio 55, Audio 81)
    - 2002
      - Rehearsals 3/19-20, 2002-03; 9 DTRS tapes; 3 DATs; 5 CD-Rs (Audio 56, Audio 81)
      - World On Seven Strings Show. Bucky Pizzarelli, 2002-03-20; 3 DTRS tapes; 2 DATs; 1 CD-R (Audio 56, Audio 81)
      - Nat King Cole Show. With John Pizzarelli, 2002-03-20; 3 DTRS tapes; 2 DATs (Audio 56)
      - Trombone, Stage Door (1940's Canteen) Rehearsals 11/22 and 11/26, 2002-11; 2 audiocassettes; 1 CD-R (Audio 77, Audio 82)
      - 40s USO show. Rehearsals, Pickups 12/9-10; Show 12/10, 2002-12; 6 DTRS tapes; 3 DATs; 3 CD-Rs (Audio 82, Audio 56)
      - Trombone Madness. Rehearsals 12/9-10 and Show 12/10, 2002-12; 6 DTRS tapes; 3 DATs; 6 CD-Rs (Audio 82, Audio 56, Audio 77)
      - McD Tribute, 2002-12-10; 1 DAT; 1 CD-R (Audio 82, Audio 56)
      - production elements, 2002; 9 CD-Rs; 1 DAT (Audio 56, Audio 82)
        New Mixes- Jersey Bounce, Opus; RW 12/02 Production Pieces; McD T-Bone CD Final? 11/20/02; Canteen HRs; 40's Canteen Production Pieces 11/27/02; S.A. 12/02 P.P. Master; Doc Severinson Tribute to General McD 10/17/02; Afternoon Piano Tags (John Sheridan); 40's USO/Trombone Pick Ups
    - 2003
      - Rehearsals and Voicetrack/Pickups, 2003-12-02; 4 DATs; 4 CD-Rs (Audio 82, Audio 57)
      - JCJB With Vernel Bagneris. Storyville Rehearsals 12/1-2, 2003-12; 11 DTRS tape; 2 DATS; 4 CD-Rs (Audio 82, Audio 57)
      - JCJB With Vernel Bagneris. Storyville Show, 2003-12-02; 3 DTRS tapes; 2 DATS; 1 CD-R (Audio 57, Audio 82)
      - JCJB With Vernel Bagneris. Nightclub Rehearsals and Pickups 12/1-2, 2003-12; 3 DTRS tapes; 2 DATs; 4 CD-Rs (Audio 57, Audio 82)
      - JCJB With Vernel Bagneris. Nightclub Show, 2003-12-02; 3 DTRS tapes; 2 DATs; 1 CD-R (Audio 82, Audio 57)
      - production elements, 2002; 7 CD-Rs (Audio 82)
        JCJB Vernel's Rehearsal CD; Tunes Sent By Vernel 10/21/03; Tunes From Jim Cullum 11/21/03; RW Remixes- 1919 Rag, Hot Man; Hot Tamale Man; Production Pieces 11/26/03; Rehearsal for Vernel 11/4/03
    - 2004
      - JCJB With Vernel Bagneris. WIZ-OZ, Bunk Show Rehearsals, 2004-5-10; 3 DTRS tapes (Audio 58)
      - JCJB With Vernel Bagneris, David Holt, Kenny Davern. Pick Ups, Vox Pick Ups 5/11 and 5/13. Bunk, Blues, Oz, 2004-05; 6 DATs; 7 CD-Rs (Audio 57, Audio 82)
      - Jim Cullum Presentation, Live Special Pre-Show, 2004-05-11; 1 DAT; 1 CD-R (Audio 58)
      - JCJB With Kenny Davern. KD Tribute, KD Blues Rehearsals, Sound Check, Pick Ups 5/12-13, 2004-05; 9 DTRS tapes; 3 DATs; 5 CD-Rs (Audio 58, Audio 82)
      - JCJB With Kenny Davern. KD Tribute, 2004-05-13; 3 DTRS tapes; 1 DAT; 1 CD-R (Audio 58, Audio 82)
      - JCJB With Kenny Davern. KD Blues, 2004-05-13; 3 DTRS tapes; 1 DAT; 1 CD-R (Audio 82, Audio 58)
      - Jim Cullum Jazz Band. JCJB Jam, 2004-05-13; 3 DTRS tapes; 1 DAT; 2 CD-Rs (Audio 82, Audio 59)
      - RW Jam Mixes May 04, 2004-12-01; 1 CD-R (Audio 82)
      - JCJB With Vernel Bagneris. WIZ-OZ Rehearsals, Vox Pick Ups, 2004-05-10; 3 DTRS tapes; 2 DATs; 2 CD-Rs (Audio 58, Audio 82)
      - JCJB With Vernel Bagneris. WIZ-OZ, 2004-05-11; 3 DTRS tapes; 1 DAT; 1 CD-R (Audio 82, Audio 59)
      - Oz Remix, 2004-08-05; 2 CD-Rs (Audio 82)
      - JCJB With Vernel Bagneris. Bunk Show Rehearsals, Pick Ups 5/10-11, 2004-05; 6 DTRS tapes; 3 DATs; 2 CD-Rs (Audio 58, Audio 59, Audio 82)
      - JCJB With Vernel Bagneris. Bunk Show, 2004-05-11; 3 DTRS tapes; 1 DAT; 1 CD-R (Audio 82, Audio 59)
      - production elements, 2004; 15 CD-Rs (Audio 82)
        Bunk Johnson HR Pieces 4/30/04; One Sweet Letter Crossfade 5/5/04; Bunk Johnson Whistling HR 5/3/04; Bunk Whistling; Wiz-Oz SFX 4/28/04; Wiz-Oz Seperate Storm FX TRacks 5/3/04; Chris-Vernel Oz Voice Tracks; Vernel Wiz-Oz Voice Tracks to be Processed; Vernel Oz Vox 4/30/04; Vernel Oz Vox 5/3/04; Nightspell Intro Pre-Build 5/4/04; Hot Tamale Man; Spare Production Parts
      - JCJB With Bob Barnard. Ballad, Riff Show P.M. Pick Ups 9/14-15, 2004-09; 3 DTRS tapes; 2 DATs; 3 CD-Rs (Audio 77, Audio 83, Audio 59)
      - JCJB With Bob Barnard. Ballad Show Rehearsal, Pick Ups and Production Pieces, 2004-09-14; 3 DTRS tapes; 1 DAT; 6 CD-Rs (Audio 77, Audio 59, Audio 83)
      - JCJB With Bob Barnard. Ballad Show, 2004-09-15; 3 DTRS tapes; 1 DAT; 1 CD-R (Audio 77, Audio 80, Audio 59)
      - JCJB With Bob Barnard. Riff Show Rehearsals, Production Pieces, 2004-09-14; 2 DATs; 3 CD-Rs (Audio 77, Audio 83)
      - JCJB With Bob Barnard. Riff Show, 2004-09-15; 3 DTRS tapes; 1 DAT; 1 CD-R (Audio 59, Audio 77, Audio 83)
      - JCJB With Bob Barnard. Jam I, II, 2004-09-15; 3 DTRS tapes; 1 DAT; 2 CD-Rs (Audio 59, Audio 77, Audio 83)
      - RW Jam Fixes, 2004-10-29; 2 CD-Rs (Audio 83)
    - 2005
      - JCJB With Vernel and Topsy, Evan C., David Holt, Vernel Bagneris. Blues and Tents, Butter and Susie, Tio Family Dynasty, Licorice Stick. Pick Ups, Vox Pick Ups 5/10-12, 2005-05; 4 DATs; 4 CD-Rs (Audio 60, Audio 83)
      - JCJB With Vernel and Topsy. Blues and Tents Rehearsal 4/11, 5/9, 2005; 1 DAT; 3 CD-Rs (Audio 83, Audio 60)
      - JCJB With Vernel and Topsy. Blues and Tents, 2005-05-10; 3 DTRS tapes; 1 DAT; 1 CD-R (Audio 60, Audio 83)
      - JCJB With Vernel and Topsy. Butter and Susie Rehearsal 4/11, 5/0, 2005; 1 DAT; 3 CD-Rs (Audio 83, Audio 60)
      - JCJB With Vernel and Topsy. Butter and Susie, 2005-05-10; 3 DTRS tapes; 1 DAT; 1 CD-R (Audio 60, Audio 83)
      - JCJB With Evan C. Licorice Stick Rehearsals 4/26, 5/11, 2005; 1 DAT; 3 CD-Rs (Audio 83, Audio 60)
      - JCJB With Evan C. Licorice Stick, 2005-05-12; 3 DTRS tapes; 1 DAT; 1 CD-R (Audio 83, Audio 60)
      - JCJB With Evan C. Tio Family Rehearsals 4/26, 5/11, 2005; 1 DAT; 3 CD-Rs (Audio 83, Audio 60)
      - JCJB With Evan C. Tio Family Dyn, 2005-05-12; 3 DTRS tapes; 1 DAT; 1 CD-R (Audio 60, Audio 83)
      - JCJB With Evan C. Jam Set, 2005-05-12; 3 DTRS tapes; 1 DAT; 3 CD-Rs (Audio 83, Audio 60)
      - RW May 2005 Jam Remix, 1 CD-R (Audio 83)
      - JCJB With Vernel and Topsy. Clarence Williams, Bordellos Rehearsals and Pick Ups 12/12-14, 2005-12; 12 DTRS tapes; 6 DATs; 9 CD-Rs (Audio 61, Audio 79, Audio 60, Audio 83)
      - JCJB With Vernel and Topsy. Bordellos, 2005-12-14; 3 DTRS tapes; 1 DAT; 1 CD-R (Audio 79, Audio 61, Audio 83)
      - JCJB With Vernel and Topsy. Clarence Williams, 2005-12-14; 3 DTRS tapes; 1 DAT; 1 CD-R (Audio 61, Audio 79, Audio 83)
      - JCJB With Topsy Chapman. Jam Show, 2005-12-15; 3 DTRS tapes; 1 DAT; 1 CD-R (Audio 61, Audio 79, Audio 83)
      - Production Pieces, 2005-12; 11 CD-R (Audio 83)
    - 2006
      - JCJB With Topsy and Dick. Teddy Wilson, Dick Hyman Tribute Rehearsals, Pick Ups and Vox Pick Ups 5/15-16, 2006-05; 9 DTRS tapes; 4 DATs; 7 CD-Rs (Audio 61, Audio 83, Audio 79)
      - JCJB With Topsy Chapman and Dick Hyman. Tribute Pre-Show, 2006-05-16; 1 DAT; 1 CD-R (Audio 79, Audio 83)
      - JCJB With Topsy and Dick. Teddy Wilson, 2006-05-16; 3 DTRS tapes; 1 DAT; 2 CD-Rs (Audio 79, Audio 61, Audio 83)
      - JCJB With Topsy and Dick. Dick Hyman Tribute, 2006-05-16; 3 DTRS tapes; 1 DAT; 1 CD-R (Audio 61, Audio 83, Audio 79)
      - JCJB With Dick Hyman. SP ST Stomp, 2006-05-16; 3 DTRS tapes; 1 DAT; 1 CD-R (Audio 62, Audio 83)
      - Jim Hayne Tribute Interview, 2005-05-16; 4 CD-Rs (Audio 83)
      - production pieces, 2005-05; 4 CD-Rs (Audio 83)
    - 2007
      - JCJB With Vernel Bagneris, Shelley Berg, David Holt. James P. Johnson, Art Tatum Pick Ups, Vox Pick Ups, 2007-05-03; 2 DATs; 2 CD-Rs (Audio 84, Audio 63)
      - JCJB With Vernel Bagneris and Shelley Berg. James P. Johnson Rehearsals, 2007-05-02; 6 DTRS tapes; 2 DATs; 2 CD-Rs (Audio 84, Audio 62)
      - JCJB With Vernel Bagneris and Shelley Berg. James P. Johnson show, 2007-05-03; 3 DTRS tapes; 1 DAT; 1 CD-R (Audio 63, Audio 84)
      - JCJB With Vernel Bagneris and Shelley Berg. Art Tatum Rehearsals, 2007-05-02; 6 DTRS tapes; 1 DAT; 2 CD-Rs (Audio 84, Audio 62)
      - JCJB With Vernel Bagneris and Shelley Berg. Art Tatum show, 2007-05-03; 3 DTRS tapes; 1 DAT; 2 CD-Rs (Audio 63, Audio 84)
      - JCJB With Vernel Bagneris and Shelley Berg. Jam Show, 2007-05-03; 3 DTRS tapes; 1 DAT; 2 CD-Rs (Audio 63, Audio 84)
      - RW May 2007 Jam Remixes, 2007-05; 2 CD-Rs (Audio 84)
      - production elements, remixes, truck logs, 2007-05; 5 CD-Rs (Audio 84)
      - JCJB, Bria Skonberg, Dave Bennett, David Holt Pick Ups 12/12-13, 2007-12; 3 DTRS tapes; 2 DATs; 2 CD-Rs (Audio 63, Audio 84)